esources.co.uk 2016-10-13

# eSources UK - Privacy Policy

eSources.co.uk Privacy Policy

Last Updated: 12th February 2006

At eSources.co.uk we know you care about how your information is treated. We comply with the Data Protection Act 1998 and we have put in place policies and procedures to ensure your privacy is protected.

Collection and Use of Personal Information

The information you provide helps us improve your sourcing and selling experience. We use this information to manage your account and to communicate with you about our services. We also use this information to prevent abuse of our website.

Does eSources.co.uk Share the Information It Receives?

Information about our users is an important part of our business, we are not in the business of selling it to others. We may share customer information only as described below, under controls that are either subject to this Privacy Policy or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Policy:

  * **Agents:**  
we employ companies to perform some functions on our behalf. Examples include processing credit card payments (banks) and verifying your registered details (registrars). They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. Further, they must process personal information in accordance with the UK's Data Protection Act.
  *   
**Protection of eSources.co.uk and others:**  
we release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property or safety of eSources.co.uk, our users or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for fraud protection. This does not include by any means selling, renting, sharing or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in a way that is contrary to the commitments made in this Privacy Policy.
  * **Remarketing:**  
We use AdWords remarketing to market our sites across the web. We place a cookie on a browser, and then a 3rd party (Google) reads these cookies and may serve an ad on a 3rd party site. You may opt out of this ad serving on Google's opt out page. If you are concerned about 3rd party cookies served by networks, you should also visit the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Information Security

  * We work to protect the security of your information by using 128 Bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) transmission, which encrypts information you input using the highest industry security standards.
  * We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of personally identifiable customer information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you.
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to Log Out when you finish using a shared computer.

Conditions of Use and Revisions

If you choose to visit eSources.co.uk, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages and application of the laws of England. If you have any concern about privacy at eSources.co.uk, please [send a thorough description](https://www.esources.co.uk/contactus.php) and we will try to resolve it.

Our business changes constantly and our Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use may also change. You should check our website frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
